现在你已经知道
Now that you know how to create an
如何建立一个任意复杂的嵌套布局，重要的是明白，
arbitrarily complex nested layout, it's important to understand
它并不是毫无限制的。再次强调，
that they don't come for free. Once again,
平台对资源的约束阻止了这一点。
the resource constraints of the platform spoil the party.
解析复杂布局可能花费很高，
[SOUND] Inflating complex layouts can be expensive, potentially
也可能影响你的程序的运行速度和响应时间。
impacting the performance and responsiveness of your app.
因此，这有两个经验之谈。
So there are two good rules of thumb
一、让你的布局浅而宽，
to help. First, keep your layout shallow and wide,
而不是深而窄。这意思是，
rather than deep and narrow. That means you're better
最好多一点同级关系，而不是父子关系。
off with more siblings and fewer children. Because it's
因为它并不这么简单，我相信你也想避免过多的视图。
never as simple as that, you also want to
通常情况下，
avoid having excessive views. In the most general terms, that
在你的整个activity层次中，不应该有超过10层的嵌套视图，
means your activities' full hierarchy should never have more
或者全部视图数不能超过80个。
than ten nested views or over 80 views in
这听起来像是有很多要求，
total. That probably sounds like a lot, but let's
不过让我们打开Android studio中的Hierarchy Viewer，
open up the Hierarchy Viewer tool in Android studio and
来看看视图多少和速度的关系是怎样的。
see just how quickly that can add up